prorealcode.com 2016-11-21

# Privacy Policy | ProRealTime trading

**PRIVACY POLICY  
**

**Last update: 22.02.2016**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ProRealCode collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (hereinafter “ **User** ” or “ **Users** ”) of the [www.prorealcode.com](http://www.prorealcode.com/) website (“ **Site** ”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ProRealCode.

**1/ Consent**

By using our Site, you agree to follow and be bound by the following privacy policy.

**2/ Personal identification information  
**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for an email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

In application of the Data Protection Act of January 6th, 1978 ( _loi Informatique et Libertés_ ), ProRealCode carries out all formal declarations of its data processing and will only carry out processing for purposes which are compatible with the Site and the Services. The data will be stored for a period which is not longer than the period necessary for the purposes of the Site and of the Services.

The User is informed that, pursuant to Section 32 of the Data Protection Act of January 6th, 1978, as amended, information disclosed through the forms available on the Site are required to respond the User’s request and are only intended for ProRealCode, which is responsible for data processing, for administrative and commercial purposes.

**3/ Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**4/ Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “ **cookies** ” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**5/ How we use collected information**

ProRealCode may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _– To improve the community and the customer’s services_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _– To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address of the User with his prior consent, to send User information and updates about the community. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include community news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, User may contact us via our Site or at the following address: [privacy@prorealcode.com](mailto:privacy@prorealcode.com)

**6/ Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.

**7/ Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**8/ Deletion of personal information**

The Users are further informed that according to the Data Protection Act of January 6th, 1978 they have at any time, a right of access, of rectification and of deletion of their personal data, on the condition of proving their identity, by contacting us at the following address: [privacy@prorealcode.com](mailto:privacy@prorealcode.com).

**9/ Terms and conditions of use of the site**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions of Use establishing the use, disclaimers and limitation of liability governing the use of the Site at: <http://www.prorealcode.com/terms-and-conditions/>

**10/ Changes to this privacy policy**

ProRealCode has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. If ProRealCode decide to change this privacy policy, ProRealCode will post those changes on this page.

You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
